import { ExerciseType } from "../../type";

export const ModuleOneExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question: "What is a cryptocurrency?",
    correctAnswer: "A digital currency based on cryptographic technology",
    falseAnswers: [
      "A physical form of money",
      "A currency issued by a government",
      "Paper money",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following projects is considered the first cryptocurrency?",
    correctAnswer: "BitCoin",
    falseAnswers: ["Ethereum", "Litecoin", "Doge coin"],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the main advantages of cryptocurrencies?",
    correctAnswer: "Lack of intermediaries and decentralization",
    falseAnswers: [
      "High inflation",
      "Requires central control",
      "Low anonymity",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleTwoExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "What technology do cryptocurrencies use to store transaction data?",
    correctAnswer: "Blockchain",
    falseAnswers: ["Cloud storage", "Centralized servers", "SQL Databases"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does the term decentralization mean in the context of cryptocurrencies?",
    correctAnswer: "Distribution of data across different locations",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Control by one person",
      "Centralized management",
      "Usage only in one country",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are the key functions of cryptography in cryptocurrencies??",
    correctAnswer: "Securing transactions and ensuring anonymity",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Speeding up transaction processes",
      "Increasing the number of transactions",
      "Restricting network access",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleThreeExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following types of wallets is considered the most secure?",
    correctAnswer: "Hardware wallet",
    falseAnswers: ["Mobile wallet", "Online wallet", "Paper wallet"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be the most important factor when choosing a cryptocurrency exchange?",
    correctAnswer: "Transaction fees",
    falseAnswers: [
      "The color of the website",
      "Amount of advertisements",
      "Number of available cryptocurrencies",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the potential risks of using cryptocurrency exchanges?",
    correctAnswer: "Hacking and fraud risks",
    falseAnswers: ["Guaranteed profits", "High availability", "Low fees"],
  },
];

export const ModuleFourExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question: "What investment principle should you follow?",
    correctAnswer: "Don’t invest more than you can afford to lose",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Invest everything in one cryptocurrency",
      "Only invest when others are doing it",
      "Ignore market",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is fundamental analysis?",
    correctAnswer:
      "Evaluating the asset's value based on technical and market data",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Analyzing price charts",
      "Predicting future prices",
      "Creating market forecasts",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the key elements of an investment strategy?",
    correctAnswer: "Portfolio diversification and risk management",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Investing in a single cryptocurrency",
      "Limiting information",
      "Quick decision-making",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleFiveExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "Which order allows you to buy a cryptocurrency at the current market price?",
    correctAnswer: "Market order",
    falseAnswers: ["Limit order", "Stop-loss order", "Take-profit order"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What apps can help track the value of a cryptocurrency portfolio?",
    correctAnswer: "Portfolio tracking apps (e.g., Blockfolio)",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Drawing apps",
      "Photo editing apps",
      "Online shopping apps",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be the first step after choosing a cryptocurrency exchange?",
    correctAnswer: "Verify your account",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Buy cryptocurrencies",
      "Set transaction limits",
      "Change the interface language",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleSixExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question: "What actions should you take to secure your cryptocurrencies?",
    correctAnswer: "Use a hardware wallet and enable 2FA",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Ignore software updates",
      "Store keys in the cloud",
      "Share personal data on untrusted sites",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is two-factor authentication (2FA)?",
    correctAnswer: "An additional layer of security when logging in",
    falseAnswers: [
      "A data encryption process",
      "A method of storing keys",
      "A type of online wallet",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are common scams associated with cryptocurrencies?",
    correctAnswer: "Fake ICOs and phishing",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Guarantees of high returns",
      "Real market analyses",
      "Increases in known cryptocurrencies",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleSevenExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question: "What is DeFi?",
    correctAnswer: "Decentralized finance",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Centralized finance",
      "Financial deficit",
      "Only for large investors",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the main risks associated with investing in NFTs?",
    correctAnswer: "Lack of regulation and price volatility",
    falseAnswers: ["High liquidity", "High availability", "Guaranteed profits"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are the major differences in cryptocurrency regulations across different ",
    correctAnswer: "Different approaches to taxation and legality",
    falseAnswers: [
      "There are the same rules everywhere",
      "Cryptocurrencies are banned everywhere",
      "It doesn’t matter for investors",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleEightExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question: "What are the key elements of an effective investment strategy?",
    correctAnswer: "Setting goals and managing risk",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Ignoring markets",
      "Investing only in one cryptocurrency",
      "Making emotional decisions",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is a stop-loss order?",
    correctAnswer: "An order for automatic sale at a price drop",
    falseAnswers: [
      "An upper investment limit",
      "A type of wallet",
      "A technical analysis process",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What methods are recommended for monitoring investment performance?",
    correctAnswer: "Regular portfolio analysis and strategy adjustments",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Daily market changes",
      "Changing investments every week",
      "Ignoring changes in the industry",
    ],
  },
];

export const ModuleNineExcercises: ExerciseType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "What are the ethical challenges associated with cryptocurrencies?",
    correctAnswer: "Environmental impact and money laundering",
    falseAnswers: ["High prices", "Trust in the market", "Low returns"],
  },
  {
    question: "Why is responsible investing important?",
    correctAnswer: "To minimize risk and positively impact communities",
    falseAnswers: [
      "To gain quick profits",
      "To avoid regulations",
      "To buy more cryptocurrencies",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the best practices for responsible investing?",
    correctAnswer: "Researching projects and analyzing risks",
    falseAnswers: [
      "Ignoring market information",
      "Investing in unknown projects",
      "Investing solely based on friends' recommendations",
    ],
  },
];

export const FullExcercises: ExerciseType[][] = [
  ModuleOneExcercises,
  ModuleTwoExcercises,
  ModuleThreeExcercises,
  ModuleFourExcercises,
  ModuleFiveExcercises,
  ModuleSixExcercises,
  ModuleSevenExcercises,
  ModuleEightExcercises,
  ModuleNineExcercises,
];
